Bhaiya, what kind of plate of dry puris was that?
10 will yield three, 20 will yield seven.
Okay, put two plates of Rs 10 each.
Okay, I'll put it on now.
Golgappa golgappa round round round
hot chole [screaming voice]
beautiful.
Here you go brother, two plates of dry puris for Rs 10 each.
Wow, wow, wow, wow, wow.
Wow brother, your dry puri is very nice.
Do one thing, put two plates of Rs. 20 each in dry
puris.  Two plates, okay, I will serve it right now.
Wow, what a scene! Here you go,
two plates of dry puris. Not only
this, now listen,
brother, take this for you.
₹40. How is this ₹40? This is only ₹
20. ₹20. And your dry puris worth 10 each are
₹40. Bhaiya, I
applied lime [laughs] and you
got seven puris for ₹10.
Wow, what a brain you used [laughs]